Support Admin Watch on kissasia.cam or kisskh.org
دعم المشرف شاهد على kissasia.cam أو kisskh.org
Hurry, hurry, hurry!
عجل، عجل، عجل!
Who told you that?
من أخبرك بذلك؟
I heard it from the Imperial Sister-in-law.
سمعت ذلك من زوجة الأخ الإمبراطوري.
She said the Imperial Brother is sending you to Mou County.
قالت إن الأخ الإمبراطوري سيرسلك إلى مقاطعة مو.
I'm afraid I won't see you for a long time.
أخشى أنني لن أراك لفترة طويلة.
Don't worry.
لا تقلق.
I'll come back safe and sound.
سأعود سالماً معافى.
It's getting late.
لقد أصبح الوقت متأخرًا.
Princess, you should return to the palace.
يا أميرة، يجب عليكِ العودة إلى القصر.
I should go too.
ينبغي أن أذهب أيضاً.
Young Duke, let me go with you.
أيها الدوق الشاب، دعني أذهب معك.
Shuang'er is right.
شوانغ إير محقة.
She's thoughtful and can look after you on the road.
إنها حنونة وتستطيع الاعتناء بك أثناء السفر.
Shuang'er is skilled in martial arts.
شوانغ إير ماهرة في فنون الدفاع عن النفس.
How do you know that?
كيف عرفت ذلك؟
That day, you were in my father's study.
في ذلك اليوم، كنتَ في مكتب والدي.
I knew everything.
لقد عرفت كل شئ.
But what you were looking for
لكن ما كنت تبحث عنه
wasn't in the study.
لم يكن ضمن الدراسة.
The road ahead is dangerous.
الطريق أمامنا خطير.
You must be careful.
يجب عليك أن تكون حذرا.
I'm leaving.
انا ذاهب.
Let's go.
دعنا نذهب.
Come.
يأتي.
Shi Feifan.
شي فيفان.
I'll wait for your safe return.
سأنتظر عودتك سالما.
Everyone, stay alert.
الجميع، ابقوا متيقظين.
Soon, Shi Feifan won't make it back.
قريبًا، لن يتمكن شي فيفان من العودة.
Yes.
نعم.
Young Duke.
الدوق الشاب.
I smell blood.
أشم رائحة دم.
The mantis hunts the cicada, unaware of the oriole.
يصطاد فرس النبي حشرة الزيز، غير مدرك لوجود طائر الصفير.
Let's go.
دعنا نذهب.
Ziyan.
ضرر.
You betrayed Celestial Star Tower.
لقد خنت برج النجمة السماوية.
You're annoying.
أنت مزعج.
Your Highness.
صاحب السمو.
This is a small token of my respect.
هذا عربون بسيط من احترامي.
It's especially for Your Highness.
هذا خاص بصاحب السمو.
I wonder why Your Highness came here this time.
أتساءل لماذا حضر سموكم إلى هنا هذه المرة.
Is there something important?
هل هناك شيء مهم؟
This time, I came
هذه المرة، جئت
to take care of someone.
أن يعتني بشخص ما.
Rest assured, Your Highness.
اطمئن يا صاحب السمو.
No matter who it is,
بغض النظر عمن هو،
he won't leave Mou County alive.
لن يغادر مقاطعة مو حياً.
Shi Feifan.
شي فيفان.
Even if you escape the ambush ahead,
حتى لو نجوت من الكمين الذي ينتظرك،
you can't escape the net here.
لا يمكنك الهروب من هذه الشبكة.
Brave one, wait!
أيها الشجاع، انتظر!
Did you come from Mou County, sir?
هل أتيت من مقاطعة مو يا سيدي؟
I've heard Mou County is beautiful.
سمعت أن مقاطعة مو جميلة.
I'm planning to visit there.
أخطط لزيارة ذلك المكان.
Brother,
أخ،
you really can't go to Mou County now.
لا يمكنك الذهاب إلى مقاطعة مو الآن.
Why is that?
لماذا هذا؟
Those damn officials in Mou County
هؤلاء المسؤولون اللعينون في مقاطعة مو
prey on the people and run wild.
يستغلون الناس ويعيشون في حالة من الفوضى.
Now the people there are homeless.
أصبح الناس هناك الآن بلا مأوى.
They can't even fill their stomachs.
إنهم لا يستطيعون حتى إشباع بطونهم.
Their suffering is beyond words.
إن معاناتهم تفوق الوصف.
You mean the damn officials prey on the people in Mou County?
هل تقصد أن المسؤولين اللعينين يستغلون الناس في مقاطعة مو؟
How do they prey on them?
كيف يصطادونها؟
Let's go.
دعنا نذهب.
Buns!
كعكات!
Fresh buns!
خبز طازج!
Hot and fresh!
ساخن وطازج!
Take a look, buns here!
ألقِ نظرة، يا كعكات هنا!
Young Duke, we've arrived.
أيها الدوق الشاب، لقد وصلنا.
Come.
يأتي.
Slow down, Young Duke.
تمهل يا دوق الصغير.
Slow down, Miss Shuang'er.
تمهلي يا آنسة شوانغ إير.
Little trinkets!
حُلي صغيرة!
Young Duke, could we be mistaken?
أيها الدوق الشاب، هل يمكن أن نكون مخطئين؟
Yeah.
نعم.
Why is Mou County busier than the Capital?
لماذا تُعتبر مقاطعة مو أكثر ازدحاماً من العاصمة؟
Latest style fans!
أحدث صيحات الموضة لمحبيها!
Come and take a look!
تعالوا وألقوا نظرة!
How much is this?
كم ثمن هذا؟
Rouge and powder!
أحمر الخدود والبودرة!
Ladies, come and see!
سيداتي، تعالوا وشاهدوا!
Beef!
لحم!
Don't look if you won't buy!
لا تنظر إذا لم تكن تنوي الشراء!
Forget it, forget it.
انسَ الأمر، انسَ الأمر.
Let's go.
دعنا نذهب.
We don't have money to buy.
ليس لدينا مال للشراء.
You're lucky today.
أنت محظوظ اليوم.
The County Magistrate said
قال قاضي المقاطعة
we must stay alert these days.
يجب أن نبقى متيقظين هذه الأيام.
Don't let anyone see a flaw.
لا تدع أحداً يرى عيباً.
Yes, yes.
نعم نعم.
Yes.
نعم.
Here, eat quickly.
تفضل، تناول الطعام بسرعة.
Eat up, eat up!
كُلْ، كُلْ!
Come on, come on!
هيا، هيا!
Grab it!
احصل عليه!
Hurry, grab it! Come on!
أسرع، احصل عليه! هيا!
Hurry, grab it!
أسرع، احصل عليه!
Aren't you hungry?
هل أنت جائع؟
Young Duke.
الدوق الشاب.
Let me go and take out those damn yamen runners.
دعني أذهب وأقضي على هؤلاء العدائين اليمنيين اللعينين.
You think I don't want to?
هل تعتقد أنني لا أريد ذلك؟
If we rush in now,
إذا اندفعنا الآن،
we'll only alert them.
سنقوم فقط بإبلاغهم.
We won't find anything.
لن نجد شيئاً.
Once you're full, go back and take my place.
بمجرد أن تشبع، عد وخذ مكاني.
If anything goes wrong,
إذا حدث أي خطأ،
your miserable life won't be spared.
لن تُستثنى حياتك البائسة.
Boss, does this really help?
يا سيدي، هل هذا مفيد حقاً؟
Those big officials from the Capital,
هؤلاء المسؤولون الكبار من العاصمة،
they all muddle through like this.
إنهم جميعاً يتخبطون هكذا.
You tell me, does it work or not?
أخبرني أنت، هل ينجح الأمر أم لا؟
Hurry back.
أسرع بالعودة.
There's important business at the yamen today.
هناك أعمال مهمة في اليمن اليوم.
Darn it!
يا إلهي!
Spare me, Young Master!
ارحمني يا سيدي الشاب!
Watch where you're going next time.
انتبه إلى أين تذهب في المرة القادمة.
You blocked my way.
لقد عرقلت طريقي.
My boots are dirty now.
حذائي متسخ الآن.
Let's go.
دعنا نذهب.
Stop looking.
توقف عن البحث.
Someone's following us.
هناك من يلاحقنا.
Here's the plan.
وهنا الخطة.
You and the Egg Yolk brothers go scout the city first.
أنت وإخوة صفار البيض تذهبون لاستكشاف المدينة أولاً.
Meet at the yamen gate at noon tomorrow.
نلتقي عند بوابة يامن ظهر غد.
Okay.
تمام.
Let's go.
دعنا نذهب.
Young Duke, what about us?
أيها الدوق الشاب، ماذا عنا؟
Thirty-Six Stratagems.
ستة وثلاثون استراتيجية.
Feint to the East, Attack to the West.
مناورة خادعة نحو الشرق، وهجوم من الغرب.
We've been tricked.
لقد تم خداعنا.
Your Highness,
صاحب السمو،
your "catching a turtle in a jar" move
حركتك "لصيد سلحفاة في جرة"
is truly brilliant.
إنه رائع حقاً.
Even if that kid has the Gatling,
حتى لو كان ذلك الطفل يمتلك مدفع جاتلينج،
he still can't escape.
لا يزال غير قادر على الهرب.
On my turf,
على أرضي،
he can't do as he pleases.
لا يستطيع أن يفعل ما يحلو له.
Your Highness, you're absolutely right.
صاحب السمو، أنت محق تماماً.
Your Highness, Shi Feifan has escaped!
يا صاحب السمو، لقد هرب شي فيفان!
What?
ماذا؟
Then hurry and chase after him!
ثم أسرع والحق به!
Where should I chase him?
أين يجب أن أطارده؟
He didn't come to the county office,
لم يأتِ إلى مكتب المقاطعة،
which means he's suspicious.
وهذا يعني أنه يشك في الأمر.
At this moment,
في هذه اللحظة،
he must be looking for a loophole.
لا بد أنه يبحث عن ثغرة قانونية.
Your Highness,
صاحب السمو،
I know of a loophole.
أعرف ثغرة قانونية.
Wujia Village.
قرية ووجيا.
Young Duke,
الدوق الشاب،
there's a girl there.
هناك فتاة هناك.
Miss, how do we get to Wujia Village?
يا آنسة، كيف نصل إلى قرية ووجيا؟
Do you know which way Wujia Village is?
هل تعرف في أي اتجاه تقع قرية ووجيا؟
Young Duke, is this girl mute?
أيها الدوق الشاب، هل هذه الفتاة خرساء؟
Don't talk nonsense.
لا تتفوه بالهراء.
Can you tell me now
هل يمكنك إخباري الآن؟
which way to go?
أي طريق نسلك؟
Can you take us there?
هل يمكنك أن تأخذنا إلى هناك؟
Where is your village chief?
أين شيخ قريتك؟